# NINA JABBARI TORKAMANI

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A passioned graphic designer who have been around advertising agencies for more than 13 years and developed 300+ graphic design projects and worked regularly on "UI&UX, PRINT DESIGN, LAYOUT, PRODUCTION MATERIALS, REBRANDING, WEB & MULTIMEDIA, PACKING, PRESENTATIONS, INFO-GRAPHICS ..." with several tech tools... (Photoshop, Indesign, Illustrator, Adobe XD, 3D Max, Flash ...)

LINKS

- https://ninajabari.github.io/cv/
- www.linkedin.com/in/nina-jabbari-torkamani

**WORK HISTORY** 

**Graphic Designer** • IranAir Airline

Tehran, Iran • December 2008 to March 2020

#### Duties:

- Design for major projects about new Airplanes (Multimedia GUI on monitor behind Aircraft seat", Aircraft body design "Livery", catering packages design, Aircraft Seat Cover Design and ...)
- Design and idea making in multiple projects in fields of Web Design, Print, Billboard,
   Advertisement Packages, graphic user interface, 3D Design...
- Presenting proposals and redesigning boarding pass and making team for its final implementation
- Magazine layout, designing of more than 60 issues of internal magazine, more than 20 special issues of in-flight magazine and more than 40 industry magazines for Pilots and Flight Safety
- Managing tasks of design team for weekly meeting in wide range and challenging projects in timely manner

# Accomplishments:

- Ideation in multimedia design for GUI airplane to minimize the costs and time without affecting the visual beauty
- . Designed Guideline uniforming in domestic and foreign branches of Iran Air
- Identity card design of stewardesses and pilots with ideas in materials and type of design for security and prevent id Identity counterfeiting
- Preparing Idea and Designing an in-flight advertising project to minimize the company's costs at the time of importing new aircraft, designing and successfully implementing the project during six months.

**Graphic Designer** • Jahan Rayaneh

Tehran, Iran • June 2006 to September 2008

### **Duties:**

- Educational software design
- Creating flyers, brochures, magazines, newspapers, and books
- Redesigning several softwares's UI and making Idea with the minimum changes in the source code of the software
- Designing characters for kid's books

## Accomplishments:

· Increasing sales of educational software by improving the UI

**Graphic Desinger** • Rasaneh Honar Tehran, Iran • July 2005 to July 2006

#### **Duties:**

- Designing exhibition stands
- . Industrial design in the fields of shop stands, advertising gifts, advertising packages
- · Urban billboard design
- · Provincial missions for promotional offers and demos of the company's ads

# Accomplishments:

• Designing dual-purpose boxes for promotional gifts in order to reuse the boxes and keep its advertising space instead of throwing them in the trash.

**EDUCATION** 

**Bachelor of Arts** - Graphic Design • *University of Applied Science and Technology* Tehran, Iran • 2015

Associate of Arts - Graphic Design • Islamic Azad University

Tehran, Iran • 2005

**CERTIFICATIONS** 

Adobe XD UI UX Design

Udemy Feb, 2023

**Illustrator 2023 Essential Training** 

LinkedIn Feb, 2023

**Graphic Brand** 

Shahid Beheshti University

Jul, 2012

**NAF-World Advertising Convention, 2nd** 

**Shahid Beheshti University** 

Jul, 2012

**TECHNICAL SKILLS** 

Adobe Photoshop Adobe XD
Adobe Illustrator 3Ds Max
Adobe In Design Adobe Flash

**LANGUAGES** 

Persian: Native language

English: B2

Upper intermediate